Severin?
You left the mines
to be here for me.
You’re my brothers.
Anyone disrespects you,
they disrespect me.
You're sitting up front.
Has he lost his mind?
Trash stays trash.
Severin!
You are out of your mind!
Count Scott, your daughter deserves better.
He's been disowned by House Carter.
Exactly.
A miner marrying a count's daughter?
It's an insult to your bloodline.
Livia is too soft-hearted.
She insisted on
going through with it.
Lady Livia is truly
devoted. such a shame.
Such a shame.
Severin!
If you don’t throw these lowborn
wretches out right now,
this wedding is over!
Severin, it’s fine.
We don’t want
to ruin your day.
You’re staying.
Severin, we know you
are a good guy.
And we’re genuinely
happy you’re marrying up.
Don't ruin your life over us.
Yeah, man.
we know you are a good guy
and we're genuinely happy you're marrying up
don't ruin your life over us
David, Jack.
You’re staying right here.
I booked this cathedral.
Today, my word is law.